[{"id":"5515","question":"<p>Indirect Distribution Channel is ________ .<\/p>\r\n","option1":"producer  \u00e2\u2020\u2019 consumer","option2":"producer \u00e2\u2020\u2019 agent","option3":"producer \u00e2\u2020\u2019 retailer","option4":"producer \u00e2\u2020\u2019 agent \u00e2\u2020\u2019 wholesaler \u00e2\u2020\u2019retailer \u00e2\u2020\u2019consumer","option5":"All of the above","correct_option":"producer \u00e2\u2020\u2019 agent \u00e2\u2020\u2019 wholesaler \u00e2\u2020\u2019retailer \u00e2\u2020\u2019consumer","qa_date":"2015-12-23 23:02:58","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"5514","question":"<p>Which is the channel of direct distribution?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Own sales showroom","option2":"Own salesmen","option3":"Own sales shops","option4":"Mail order","option5":"All of the above","correct_option":"All of the above","qa_date":"2015-12-23 22:58:58","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"5518","question":"<p>Which is the factor of distribution channel?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Number of customer ","option2":"Size of the manufacture","option3":"Product weight","option4":"Perishability","option5":"All of the above","correct_option":"All of the above","qa_date":"2015-12-23 23:04:21","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"5513","question":"<p>The function of distribution channel includes _________ .<\/p>\r\n","option1":"managing finances","option2":"promotional activities","option3":"fixing prices","option4":"servicing the consumer","option5":"All of the above","correct_option":"All of the above","qa_date":"2015-12-23 22:58:58","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"5520","question":"<p>Which of the following factors influences the choice of distribution channel?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Product consideration","option2":"Market consideration","option3":"Company consideration","option4":"Middlemen consideration","option5":"All of the above","correct_option":"All of the above","qa_date":"2015-12-23 23:06:52","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"5522","question":"<p>The type of distribution Channel is<\/p>\r\n","option1":"producer\u00e2\u2020\u2019 consumer \u00e2\u2020\u2019agent \u00e2\u2020\u2019wholesaler \u00e2\u2020\u2019retailer ","option2":"producer \u00e2\u2020\u2019agent \u00e2\u2020\u2019wholesaler \u00e2\u2020\u2019retailer \u00e2\u2020\u2019consumer","option3":"agent \u00e2\u2020\u2019 consumer \u00e2\u2020\u2019wholesaler \u00e2\u2020\u2019 producer \u00e2\u2020\u2019retailer","option4":"retailer \u00e2\u2020\u2019 consumer \u00e2\u2020\u2019producer \u00e2\u2020\u2019wholesaler \u00e2\u2020\u2019 agent ","option5":"consumer \u00e2\u2020\u2019 producer \u00e2\u2020\u2019wholesaler \u00e2\u2020\u2019agent \u00e2\u2020\u2019retailer","correct_option":"producer \u00e2\u2020\u2019agent \u00e2\u2020\u2019wholesaler \u00e2\u2020\u2019retailer \u00e2\u2020\u2019consumer","qa_date":"2015-12-23 23:09:27","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"5516","question":"<p>Distribution Channels are<\/p>\r\n","option1":"system of economic institution through which a producer of goods delivers them into hands to their uses","option2":"system of pricing","option3":"costing system","option4":"branding","option5":"All of the above","correct_option":"system of economic institution through which a producer of goods delivers them into hands to their uses","qa_date":"2015-12-23 23:02:58","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"5521","question":"<p>The channel of distribution comes under which element of the marketing mix?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Product","option2":"Price","option3":"Place  ","option4":"Promotion","option5":"None of these  ","correct_option":"Place  ","qa_date":"2015-12-23 23:09:27","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"5519","question":"<p>Vending machine is&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"a pricing system","option2":"distribution channel","option3":"cost planning","option4":"management system","option5":"All of these","correct_option":"distribution channel","qa_date":"2015-12-23 23:06:52","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""},{"id":"5517","question":"<p>Marketing channels are&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n","option1":"distribution network through which producer\u00e2\u20ac\u2122s products of goods delivers them into hands of their uses.","option2":"the channel of storage","option3":"channel of production ","option4":"All of the above","option5":"None of the above","correct_option":"distribution network through which producer\u00e2\u20ac\u2122s products of goods delivers them into hands of their uses.","qa_date":"2015-12-23 23:02:58","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":""}]